{
  "1" : {
    "question" : "True or false: \\(\\frac {1} {4} = \\frac {2} {8}\\)?",
    "answer" : 0,
    "options" : ["True", "False"],
    "explanation" : "True. \\(1 \\times 8 = 8\\), and \\(2 \\times 4 = 8\\)."
  },
  "2" : {
    "question" : "True or false: \\(\\frac {2} {8} = \\frac {8} {32}\\)?",
    "answer" : 0,
    "options" : ["True", "False"],
    "explanation" : "True. \\(2 \\times 32 = 64\\), and \\(8 \\times 8 = 64\\)."
  },
  "3" : {
    "question" : "True or false: \\(\\frac {4} {11} = \\frac {10} {22}\\)?",
    "answer" : 1,
    "options" : ["True", "False"],
    "explanation" : "False. \\(4 \\times 22 = 88\\), but \\(10 \\times 11 = 110\\)."
  },
  "4" : {
    "question" : "True or false: \\(\\frac {7} {11} = \\frac {14} {22}\\)?",
    "answer" : 0,
    "options" : ["True", "False"],
    "explanation" : "True. \\(7 \\times 22 = 154\\), and \\(14 \\times 11 = 154\\)."
  },
  "5" : {
    "question" : "True or false: \\(\\frac {6} {7} = \\frac {26} {28}\\)?",
    "answer" : 1,
    "options" : ["True", "False"],
    "explanation" : "False. \\(6 \\times 28 = 168\\), but \\(26 \\times 7 = 182\\)."
  },
  "6" : {
    "question" : "True or false: \\(\\frac {1} {3} = \\frac {3} {9}\\)?",
    "answer" : 0,
    "options" : ["True", "False"],
    "explanation" : "True. \\(1 \\times 9 = 9\\), and \\(3 \\times 3 = 9\\)."
  },
  "7" : {
    "question" : "True or false: \\(\\frac {3} {10} = \\frac {9} {30}\\)?",
    "answer" : 0,
    "options" : ["True", "False"],
    "explanation" : "True. \\(3 \\times 30 = 90\\), and \\(9 \\times 10 = 90\\)."
  },
  "8" : {
    "question" : "True or false: \\(\\frac {2} {3} = \\frac {8} {12}\\)?",
    "answer" : 0,
    "options" : ["True", "False"],
    "explanation" : "True. \\(2 \\times 12 = 24\\), and \\(8 \\times 3 = 24\\)."
  },
  "9" : {
    "question" : "True or false: \\(\\frac {6} {12} = \\frac {11} {24}\\)?",
    "answer" : 1,
    "options" : ["True", "False"],
    "explanation" : "False. \\(6 \\times 24 = 144\\), but \\(11 \\times 12 = 132\\)."
  },
  "10" : {
    "question" : "True or false: \\(\\frac {4} {5} = \\frac {8} {10}\\)?",
    "answer" : 0,
    "options" : ["True", "False"],
    "explanation" : "True. \\(4 \\times 10 = 40\\), and \\(8 \\times 5 = 40\\)."
  }
}

